這忙碌的城鎮
This busy city
我眼珠轉不來
blurs so swiftly by
生命的交響曲
Symphonies of lifetimes
又一天開始
The new day arrives
而我又停不住回想，我們從前
And I can't stop from thinking about who we were
以為我知道家的處所
Thought I had known where home was
不在這，不在那
not here, nor there
而我也大可繼續夢想，以前過得怎樣
And I can spend my time dreaming of the things that used to be
或繼續走這條長途
or travel down this long path
一直在我眼前
that's been out before me
而邊走邊看烏鴉，在路途中
And going as the crow flies down the way
我們的旅途從未終點，還有更多
our journey's never over, still follow down
對方還有個世界
There's another world over
它，我知道
One that I know
我心中，我一直都在那頭
In my mind, I've always been there
我總想飛去那
how I've tried to go
每份記憶
Every memory
過往的無數條痕
residues of the moments
那道平靜，消失去
As that stillness passes by
而我看向一片晴天
and I look towards an open sky
而我也大可繼續夢想，以前過得怎樣
And I can spend my time dreaming of the things that used to be
或繼續走這條長途
or travel down this long path
一直在我眼前
that's been out before me
而邊走邊看烏鴉，在路途中
And going as the crow flies down the way
我們的旅途從未終點，還有更多
our journey's never over, still follow down